<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>⛓ Protocol on Pocket Network</title>
    <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ⛓ Protocol on Pocket Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🤝 Servicing</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/servicing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/servicing/</guid>
      <description>Overview The Pocket Network’s Servicing layer is comprised of 2 main actors: Applications and Servicers. An Application submits a Relay Request, or an API requests to be routed to any Relay Chain. A Servicer ‘services’ the Application, by routing the Relay Request to the Relay Chain and forwarding the response to the Application. This interaction between an Application and a Servicer is the fundamental utility of Pocket Network.
Basic Lifecycle To register for decentralized infrastructure, an Application must stake the native cryptocurrency POKT in the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🛡 Security</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/security/</guid>
      <description>By enforcing POKT to be staked from both the Applications and the Validators, the protocol is able to economically penalize either actor participating in servicing
Session Security The probability due to randomized selection without replacement is:
$$P (A∩B) = P (A) P (B|A)$$Thus the probability of selecting any combination of Validators at any given Session in Pocket Network is:
$$1 / (allvals (allvals-1) (allvals - 2) ... * (allvals - valspersession))$$Meaning, the more Validators in the network, the higher level of randomization and by extension security.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>