<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>🪙 Economics on Pocket Network</title>
    <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 🪙 Economics on Pocket Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🪙 Token Economics</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/token/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/token/</guid>
      <description>The Purpose of POKT POKT is not a transactional cryptocurrency. The Pocket Network blockchain is not meant to have sub-5-second block times, provide 10,000 transactions per second, facilitate direct payments (generally speaking), or act as a smart contract platform. The majority of the transactions occurring will be staking by Applications and Service Nodes, Proof-of-Relay batches by Service Nodes, and block reward payments to Service Nodes for facilitating Relay requests, which all POKT holders will pay for via inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💻 App Economics</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/apps/</guid>
      <description>Important Initial Application Parameters Item Initial Parameter Minimum Application Stake 1 POKT Minimum Unbonding Period (Apps) 21 days BaseRelaysPerPOKT 1.67 relays per session Stability Adjustment 0 Participation Rate Active False Block Time 15 minutes Session Time 4 blocks (60 minutes) Session Node Count 5 nodes Max Chains per Stake 15 Application Economics Pocket Network is a developer-driven protocol, with demand from Applications driving the rewards the Service Nodes earn. Applications use Pocket Network to retrieve data and write state to and for their blockchain applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🤖 Node Economics</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/nodes/</guid>
      <description>Overview Pocket uses Proof-of-Stake (PoS) to secure the state machine and falls under the umbrella of generalized mining or useful proofs of work, where inflation is directly tied to work validated by the network.
Service Nodes batch all requests received in a session to one Pocket blockchain transaction, a “Proof-of-Relay” that Applications can validate client-side and other nodes can validate in block production, removing the need for Applications to pay constant transaction fees for this work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🏦 Monetary Policy</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/monetary-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/monetary-policy/</guid>
      <description>Pocket&amp;rsquo;s staking and inflation mechanisms enable a more efficient resource allocation structure by limiting the number of transactions (and thus block validation costs) to one-time staking transactions. All nodes are able to focus primarily on servicing and validating Relay requests by Applications, with minimal energy spent on block validation. By being eventually consistent and tying rewards directly to inflation, Service Nodes are in effect receiving micropayments for work validated by two parties without the need for constant on-chain fee payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💰 Pricing &amp; Economics FAQ</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/faq/</guid>
      <description>What is POKT? POKT is the native utility token that powers the economics of the protocol. Pocket Network requires both developers and nodes to stake POKT to participate in the network. Nodes earn POKT for fulfilling API requests for apps on a per request basis.
How much does it cost to send a relay? This is determined by the BaseRelaysPerPOKT parameter.
How much can I earn by running a node? Pocket is quite a unique blockchain network, because there are two ways for nodes to earn POKT:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>