<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn Pocket on Pocket Network</title>
    <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learn Pocket on Pocket Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.pokt.network/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>⛓ Protocol</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol/</guid>
      <description>The Pocket Network is comprised of 3 components: Applications, Nodes and the Network Layer.
An Application submits Relays, or API requests meant to be routed to any public database node. Nodes service these Relays, by submitting them to the public databases they are meant for, and sending the response (if any) back to the Application. The Network Layer is comprised of all the rules, protocols and finality storage that serve as the backbone of the interactions between Applications and Nodes, including (but not limited to), configuration, record tracking, governance and economic policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🪙 Economics</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/economics/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR Pocket Network requires both developers and nodes to stake its native utility token, POKT, to participate in the network. Nodes earn rewards for fulfilling API requests for developers on a per request basis. POKT is permanently inflationary, but total supply will be capped through a burning mechanism put in place by the DAO, who controls the monetary policy. The final total supply of POKT will be dictated by the DAO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>👀 Future (v1)</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/future/</guid>
      <description>Pocket Network launched on mainnet on July 28th 2020, with the singular goal of providing a utilitarian economy between Web3 applications and the full nodes that provide access to the data they need. Since launching, Pocket Network has demonstrated that a decentralized alternative to full node infrastructure is not only possible, but with the right architecture could provide a service that is unmatched. Further, the lessons we have learned maintaining the network have highlighted a path towards a truly scalable future for Pocket Network’s Web3 infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/vision/</guid>
      <description>Decentralizing Web3 Access Web3 is built on incentives.
Blockchains enable unstoppable validation of transactions by incentivizing validator nodes, with mining/staking rewards, to confirm transactions. However, while this ensures an unstoppable history of transactions, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t ensure unstoppable access to read the history or to write new transactions to the history.
Many blockchain communities have debated incentivizing the RPC nodes that provide this access to the blockchain. Facing quite a complex challenge though, they have rejected on-chain solutions, expecting that altruists would run RPC nodes for the good of the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🎚 Protocol Parameters</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol-parameters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/protocol-parameters/</guid>
      <description>Off-Chain USDRelayTargetRange Current Value: $0.00036–0.00059 per relay
The range of USD/relay prices the DAO doesn’t want the real price of a relay to exceed, accounting for the USD price of POKT.
ReturnOnInvestmentTarget Current Value: 10 months
How long the DAO wants it to take for the USD/relay price to be achieved, since the cost basis of a relay decreases over the lifetime of an app stake.
Application Module ApplicationStakeMinimum Current Value: 1000000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Application The base consumer of the decentralized infrastructure of Pocket Network.
Application’s stake POKT into the protocol in order to access the decentralized infrastructure.
Application Authentication Token (AAT) An Application Authentication Token (AAT) is needed for each client to authorize the use of an allocated “throughput.”
Application Authentication Tokens are similar in function to JSON Web Tokens (JWT) and provide security guarantees for the use of the service.
An AAT is generated after a client acquires &amp;amp; stakes POKT for an application.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>