<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Pocket Network</title>
    <link>https://docs.pokt.network/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Pocket Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.pokt.network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>✅ Supported Blockchains</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/supported-blockchains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/supported-blockchains/</guid>
      <description>Pocket works out-of-the-box with any network/blockchain (RelayChain) that uses the RPC standard.
Current RelayChains The following table shows the full list of supported, revenue-generating RelayChains. This list should be identical to the SupportedBlockchains parameter.
Name Portal API Prefix RelayChainID Algorand algo-mainnet 0029 Avalanche avax-mainnet 0003 Binance Smart Chain bsc-mainnet 0004 Binance Smart Chain Archival bsc-archival 0010 Boba boba-mainnet 0048 DFKchain Subnet dfk-mainnet 03DF Evmos evmos-mainnet 0046 Ethereum eth-mainnet 0021 Ethereum Archival eth-archival 0022 Ethereum Archival Trace eth-archival-trace 0028 Ethereum Goerli eth-goerli 0026 Ethereum Kovan poa-kovan 0024 Ethereum Rinkeby eth-rinkeby 0025 Ethereum Ropsten eth-ropsten 0023 Fantom fantom-mainnet 0049 FUSE fuse-mainnet 0005 FUSE Archival fuse-archival 000A Gnosis Chain gnosischain-mainnet 0027 Gnosis Chain Archival gnosischain-archival 000C Harmony Shard 0 harmony-0 0040 IoTeX iotex-mainnet 0044 Moonbeam moonbeam-mainnet 0050 Moonriver moonriver-mainnet 0051 NEAR near-mainnet 0052 OKExChain oec-mainnet 0047 Optimism optimism-mainnet 0053 Pocket Network mainnet 0001 Polygon poly-mainnet 0009 Polygon Archival poly-archival 000B Solana sol-mainnet 0006 Swimmer Network Mainnet avax-cra 03CB Pocket Testnet RelayChains The following table shows the full list of currently-supported blockchains on the Pocket Testnet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💰 Get POKT</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/</guid>
      <description>POKT is the native cryptocurrency that powers Pocket. In this section, we&amp;rsquo;ll go over how to store your POKT safely, as well as buying and staking.
Manage POKT Buy POKT Stake POKT Wrapped POKT (wPOKT) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Pocket</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/learn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Pocket</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/use/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run Nodes</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/node/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/node/</guid>
      <description>In this section, you&amp;rsquo;ll get information on running a Pocket node.
These details are mostly for &amp;ldquo;intermediate&amp;rdquo; node runners, who are familiar with running full nodes and have the knowledge required to avoid getting lost. If you would like a more beginner&amp;rsquo;s tutorial, visit Zero To Node. You may also want to explore node-hosting services.
Want to understand the economics of running a node before you dive in? Read about Node Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/integrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/integrate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/community/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>💬 More Information</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/more-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/more-info/</guid>
      <description>Pocket Network is an open-source multi-stakeholder community. Therefore, the best way to contact us is to join our community in Discourse and Discord.
Discord You can join our Discord. We recommend doing this if you want to keep your finger on the pulse.
Be sure to start in the 👋welcome channel, where you can choose the topics you&amp;rsquo;re interested in.
Discourse (Pocket Forum) Ask for help Report a bug Request a feature Submit a proposal Ask for feedback Find or advertise node hosting services Find or advertise work in the Pocket ecosystem Social Media You can find us on the following sites:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>