<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pocket-Powered dApps on Pocket Network</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/</link><description>Recent content in Pocket-Powered dApps on Pocket Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conquest.eth</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/conquest-eth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/conquest-eth/</guid><description>We have minted a public Görli RPC endpoint with up to 10M requests per day to give players who are exploring the Conquest metaverse the opportunity to connect to Pocket&amp;rsquo;s decentralized, resilient infra!
To get started connecting to Pocket&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure for Görli testnet, do the following:
Click on the Networks drop-down menu, then press Custom RPC Under the Network Name field, write Görli Pocket Portal Within the New RPC URL field, copy and paste this endpoint URL https://eth-goerli.</description></item><item><title>Dark Forest</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/dark-forest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/dark-forest/</guid><description>{% embed url=&amp;ldquo;https://youtu.be/jxfOc4XjJaw&amp;quot; %}
We have issued an xDAI RPC endpoint that grants up to 50M requests per day (&amp;amp; 250 nodes per hour) just for Dark Forest players!
To get started connecting to Pocket&amp;rsquo;s node infrastructure for xDAI in Dark Forest, do the following:
Click on the gear icon to open the settings page If it doesn&amp;rsquo;t open automatically, click on &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; icon to expand the settings page Scroll down until you see the &amp;ldquo;Change RPC Endpoint&amp;rdquo; section Copy and paste this endpoint URL into the text boxhttps://poa-xdai.</description></item><item><title>MyCrypto</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/mycrypto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/mycrypto/</guid><description>{% embed url=&amp;ldquo;https://youtu.be/LTVNN3SBuik&amp;quot; %}
MyCrypto is an open-source, client-side tool for generating Ethereum wallets, handling ERC-20 tokens, and interacting with the blockchain more easily. Developed by and for the community since 2015, they’re focused on building awesome products that put the power in people’s hands.
This is why we want to give users an opportunity to connect to our own infrastructure!
Open the MyCrypto desktop application, if you don’t have it yet, then download it here: https://download.</description></item><item><title>Rotki</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/rotki/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/use/dapps/rotki/</guid><description>Rotki is an open-source portfolio tracker and accounting/analytics tool that protects your privacy.
We&amp;rsquo;ve sponsored a public Ethereum RPC endpoint for Rotki users in order to add an extra layer of privacy when using the application.
To get started connecting to Pocket&amp;rsquo;s censorship-resistant infrastructure for Ethereum, do the following:
1. Open and login into your local application.
2. Toggle to account, then open settings.
3. Scroll down to the Local Nodes section, then delete the default RPC endpoint.</description></item></channel></rss>