<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Pocket Network</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Pocket Network</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1 – Server setup</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/server-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/server-setup/</guid><description>This section will help you set up and configure a server to prepare it for being a Pocket node.
Setup a server The first thing you&amp;rsquo;ll need to run a Pocket node is a server. For this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll be using a virtual machine on the Linode cloud service. But, you could use any cloud service you like.
Info Pocket has no affiliation with Linode and does not recommend any one provider over another.</description></item><item><title>Part 2 – Software installation</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/software-install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/software-install/</guid><description>This section will help you install all the necessary software for your node.
Install dependencies Now let&amp;rsquo;s move on to the Pocket CLI installation.
At this point you should be logged in via SSH as the pocket user that we set up in a previous step. Before we install the Pocket software, we need to update the existing system packages and add a few dependencies.
Updating system packages Update the repository index with the following command: sudo apt update Update the distribution with the following command: sudo apt dist-upgrade -y After the update completes, we&amp;rsquo;re ready to install the dependencies.</description></item><item><title>Part 3 – Pocket configuration</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/pocket-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/pocket-config/</guid><description>This section will help you configure your instance of Pocket.
Create a Pocket wallet account Pocket nodes are associated with a Pocket wallet account. This is the account that will be used to send and receive transactions from the node. You can either create a new account using the Pocket CLI we just installed, or you can use an existing account. For this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll be creating a new account.</description></item><item><title>Part 4 – Proxy configuration</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/proxy-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/proxy-config/</guid><description>This section will help you set up the proxy setting on your node.
Setup SSL Pocket requires that nodes have an SSL certificate for secure communications. SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) is a layer of security that sits on top of TCP/IP. It&amp;rsquo;s used to encrypt the data sent between a client and a server. To use SSL, you need to have a certificate and a key. Thankfully, getting an SSL certificate is straightforward and free.</description></item><item><title>Part 5 – Going live</title><link>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/going-live/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pokt-foundation.github.io/docs-hugo/node/tutorials/zero-to-node/going-live/</guid><description>This section will details the final steps in going live with your node.
Test everything At this point your Pocket node should be up and running!
But you&amp;rsquo;ll want to test it to confirm. The following are some of the things you can do to test your Pocket Node.
Make sure the Pocket process is running The first thing to check is that the pocket service is running. You can do that by running the following command:</description></item></channel></rss>