<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>💰 Get POKT on Pocket Network</title>
    <link>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 💰 Get POKT on Pocket Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manage POKT</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/wallets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/wallets/</guid>
      <description>Before buying any POKT, you should first ensure that you know how to store it safely.
Create Wallet You can use the official wallet web app to create your wallet. Note: desktop and Ledger apps are in development. This documentation will be updated when they are available to use.
Click &amp;lsquo;Create&amp;rsquo;. 2. Enter a unique passphrase.
WarningThe passphrase unlocks/decrypts an encrypted version of the private key that is stored in a Key File.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy POKT</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/buy/</guid>
      <description>Exchanges POKT is available to purchase on multiple global exchanges. Follow this DAO proposal for updates on official listings.
Note that you can’t stake POKT from exchanges. To stake your POKT you would need to withdraw to your wallet (see below).
Over-the-Counter (OTC) Over-the-Counter (OTC) trading desks are white-label markets operated by trusted intermediaries who match buyers and sellers. They are typically used for large volume trades.
The POKT community has a number of OTC desks which can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stake POKT</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/stake/</guid>
      <description>There is no many-to-one delegation in Pocket Network. You cannot simply stake POKT from your wallet and then forget about it. A POKT account must be staked on a node that is relaying RPC requests. However, if you do not have the skills to run a node yourself, you still have options.
Run Your Own Node Running your own node is an option if you possess both of the following:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🎁 Wrapped POKT (wPOKT)</title>
      <link>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/wpokt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://docs.pokt.network/pokt/wpokt/</guid>
      <description>What is wPOKT? Wrapped POKT (wPOKT) is an ERC-20 token backed 1:1 by POKT on the Pocket blockchain and held by a POKT wallet where the underlying holdings are verifiable. wPOKT standardizes POKT to the ERC20 format, enabling and leveraging the usage of smart contracts. Check out the whole green paper here.
How does staking wPOKT contribute to the Pocket Network? Data Farming allows Ethereum users to stake for infrastructure on behalf of their favorite Ethereum applications while earning rewards.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>